export const Grammar4=[
    {
      question: "He plays basketball every day.",
      Options: [
        "Present",
        "Past",
        "Future"
      ],
      correct: 1,
      marked: -1
    },
    {
      question: "Meera will go to a concert.",
      Options: [
        "Present",
        "Past",
        "Future"
      ],
      correct: 3,
      marked: -1
    },
    {
      question: "It rained heavily.",
      Options: [
        "Present",
        "Past",
        "Future"
      ],
      correct: 1,
      marked: -1
    },
    {
      question: "The baby is crying.",
      Options: [
        "Past",
        "Present",
        "Future"
      ],
      correct: 1,
      marked: -1
    },
    {
      question: "Dogs were barking a lot.",
      Options: [
        "Past",
        "Future",
        "Present"
      ],
      correct: 2,
      marked: -1
    },
    {
      question: "The students are __________ their notes.",
      Options: [
        "Wrote",
        "Written",
        "Writing",
        "Write"
      ],
      correct: 3,
      marked: -1
    },
    {
      question: "The doctor __________ out for ten minutes.",
      Options: [
        "Go",
        "Going",
        "Gone",
        "Went"
      ],
      correct: 4,
      marked: -1
    },
    {
      question: "The new restaurant __________ last week.",
      Options: [
        "Open",
        "Opened",
        "Opening",
        "Start"
      ],
      correct: 2,
      marked: -1
    },
    {
      question: "I __________ working all afternoon and have just finished the assignment.",
      Options: [
        "have been",
        "had been",
        "shall be",
        "am"
      ],
      correct: 2,
      marked: -1
    },
    {
      question: "Rohan __________ the movie before he read the review.",
      Options: [
        "watches",
        "have watched",
        "had watched",
        "was watching"
      ],
      correct: 3,
      marked: -1
    }
  ]
  